{
    "subject": "resource/Jan_Montyn",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Oudewater",
    "human_readable": "Jan Montyn was born in Oudewater.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8398155570030212,
            "question": "Where was Jan Montyn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7586034536361694,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Jan Montyn and other individuals from Oudewater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7471081614494324,
            "question": "What year was Jan Montyn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678441166877747,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in Oudewater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3556867241859436,
            "question": "What is Oudewater known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34762924909591675,
            "question": "Does Jan Montyn have any known relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3100082576274872,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Oudewater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2756645679473877,
            "question": "Is there anything else we know about Jan Montyn's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26243841648101807,
            "question": "What is the history of Oudewater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2471269816160202,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the culture of Oudewater?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jan Montyn was born in Oudewater.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3115_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Oudewater?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3115_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else we know about Jan Montyn's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3115_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events associated with Oudewater?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3115_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3115_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Jan Montyn was born in Oudewater. This information can be found in multiple documents, including file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3115/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt, file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3115/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt, file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3115/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt, and file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3115/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Jan Montyn was born in Oudewater, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}